Samantha@Alright, everyone
Samantha@Let's stop talking about these supernatural things
Samantha@Let's drink and play some games
Samantha@Look, I've prepared a lot of stuff
Megan@I'm so full
Victoria@You ate too much, didn't you?
Victoria@It was just you two eating, right?
Megan@No way
Megan@They ate a lot too
Samantha@If we're done eating
Samantha@Shall we play the King's Game?
Victoria@A game?
Alex@Yeah, sure!
Samantha@Alright, I'll shuffle the cards
Emily@How do you play this game?
Samantha@Great
Victoria@Just play along, you'll get it
Samantha@Right
Victoria@Just draw a card, that's all
Megan@In the King's Game
Megan@The one who draws the K is the King
Megan@They can order others to do anything
Samantha@That's right, it's exciting
Samantha@You draw first
Grace@Us?
Samantha@Mm-hmm
Samantha@Go ahead, draw
Samantha@Draw
Emily@Here?
Alex@Is it the King?
Megan@No, almost
Samantha@Oh, I'm the King
Victoria@This feels scary
Victoria@Why did it have to be her?
Samantha@I choose Alex and Megan
Samantha@Kiss for 10 seconds
Samantha@Kiss
Samantha@Come on, give a kiss
@Kiss, kiss
Alex@This is so embarrassing
Alex@I'm going to kiss now
Alex@I'm shy
Alex@Don't look, don't look
Alex@Don't look
Samantha@10
Samantha@9
Samantha@8
Samantha@7
Samantha@6
Samantha@5
Victoria@That's so mean!
Samantha@4
Samantha@3
Samantha@2
Samantha@2.5
Samantha@OK
Samantha@Congratulations to you all
Alex@This is really going too far
Alex@Counting down to 2.5 like that
Samantha@Congratulations to you all
Samantha@Was it fun?
Victoria@Look, her face is all red
Megan@Of course my face is red from drinking
Victoria@Kissing a girl can make you blush too
@What are you saying? - So innocent
Megan@It's because of the alcohol
Megan@It's the drinking
Alex@Alright, next round
Alex@Take your cards
Samantha@Okay
Alex@You meanie
Samantha@Hey
Victoria@Hey
Victoria@Miss
Victoria@Move your foot
Samantha@I didn't
@You have something - No, I don't
Victoria@This is too much
Alex@That's going too far
Megan@You're cheating
Victoria@Your desire to win is stronger than your sex drive
Samantha@No, it's not like that
Samantha@I just didn't want you to feel awkward and stop playing
@You're all scared, aren't you? - That's just an excuse
Samantha@Really, I'm just trying to liven up the atmosphere
@Punishment!
Victoria@We're punishing you
Victoria@Samantha, eat a banana from between my legs for 10 seconds
Victoria@Don't break it, okay?
Samantha@Alright, I'm good at this
Samantha@Let's do it
Samantha@Come on
Victoria@Let's see how good you are
Samantha@Alright, you want to see how good I am, huh?
Samantha@See how awesome I am?
Victoria@You're done for.
Victoria@You're definitely not going to succeed. Come on.
Alex@Let me see.
Megan@That's so naughty.
Victoria@Isn't this your most familiar move?
Victoria@Look at her.
Victoria@She must have experience with countless bananas.
Megan@It broke!
Samantha@Oh, come on!
Samantha@This banana is so soft.
Samantha@Wait, who bought this?
Samantha@This banana is way too soft.
Emily@Soft ones taste better.
Emily@And they're cheaper too.
Emily@I was planning to blend it with milk to drink.
Samantha@Fine, I'll buy you another one.
Samantha@Well, in that case...
Samantha@You should be punished along with me.
Victoria@Sure, no problem.
Victoria@Let's continue and draw again.
Victoria@Come on.
Victoria@I'm not afraid of you.
Megan@They're so naughty.
Megan@One more time.
Victoria@Give me the last card.
Megan@Okay.
Megan@I want this one.
Samantha@Ladies and gentlemen,
Samantha@Prepare to feel the queen's power!
Samantha@Hey, Megan,
Samantha@Go lick Emily's nipple for 10 seconds.
Samantha@The loser gets punished, you know.
@Do we have to? - She'll be embarrassed.
Emily@Does she have to expose her nipple?
Victoria@Lick the nipple.
Samantha@You have to honor the bet.
@Lick the nipple. - Honor the bet.
Victoria@Lick the nipple.
Samantha@Get into position.
Megan@Alright.
Megan@It'll be over in the blink of an eye.
Samantha@Come on!
Victoria@She's not wearing anything underneath.
Samantha@So naughty!
Victoria@It's all perked up.
Samantha@Look at that nimble tongue.
Victoria@It's so ticklish!
Samantha@I forgot where I was in the count.
Samantha@10
Samantha@9
Samantha@8
Samantha@7
Samantha@6
Samantha@5
Samantha@4
Samantha@3.5
Samantha@2
Samantha@2.5
Samantha@1
Samantha@Congratulations to you both!
Samantha@You did great!
Samantha@That was amazing, congratulations!
Samantha@So exciting!
Megan@Let's draw again.
Megan@I don't believe this.
Victoria@Yeah, one more time.
Victoria@How is it her again?
Megan@One more time.
Megan@You win every time, it's not fair.
Samantha@Okay, this is my last card.
Samantha@This is really my last one.
Megan@I don't believe it either.
Alex@This is ridiculous, we didn't get any.
Samantha@Ladies and gentlemen, it's me again!
Samantha@See? I really do have the aura of a queen, don't I?
Alex@Are you sure you're not cheating?
Samantha@I'm really not cheating.
Samantha@The cards weren't even in my hands just now.
Samantha@This time, I'm going to choose.
Victoria@This is too much!
Samantha@I choose...
Samantha@I choose you and Emily.
Samantha@Face wash for 10 seconds.
Grace@It's you again.
Emily@What's a face wash?
Samantha@You don't know what a face wash is?
Samantha@A face wash is like this...
Emily@Why is it me again?
@Just do it! - Because you're so cute!
Samantha@Well, in that case...
Samantha@Wouldn't it look better if we take off our clothes?
Victoria@Okay.
Samantha@That's the spirit!
Samantha@This is so exciting!
Megan@Look at them.
Emily@I can't do this.
Emily@I'm sorry.
Emily@I can't breathe.
Emily@It's a bit too embarrassing.
Samantha@In that case, you'll be considered as failing.
Samantha@Yeah, you're failing if you do this.
Megan@No way.
Victoria@It's fine. We can punish them later anyway.
Samantha@Alright then.
Samantha@Haven't we missed someone who hasn't played the game yet?
Victoria@Who?
Samantha@Oh, Grace.
Samantha@Grace hasn't played the game.
Megan@She finished eating it.
Samantha@You're unbelievable!
Samantha@Then whoever draws the King next...
Samantha@...has to choose Grace, okay?
Megan@Okay.
Samantha@For real, alright? Come on.
Samantha@Let's draw again.
Samantha@Time to draw cards!
Victoria@It can't possibly be her again, right?
Megan@This one.
Megan@Not again.
Megan@It's not me.
Samantha@Okay, it's not me this time.
Emily@It's me!
Emily@What should I do?
@You have to - You must choose her.
Samantha@Choose Grace.
Samantha@Come on, the easiest thing is to...
Samantha@Say something naughty.
Emily@Then I choose Grace.
Emily@Peel a banana with your foot.
Samantha@What kind of dare is that?
Samantha@Is that supposed to be naughty?
Emily@It can be.
Samantha@Let's try it.
Samantha@Where's the banana?
Megan@Here it is.
Grace@I think I can do it.
Samantha@Really?
Grace@It's quite difficult.
@Come on. - Why are you putting it there?
Samantha@Alright, go ahead and try.
Samantha@How are you going to do it?
Grace@I don't know.
Victoria@It seems difficult.
Victoria@You need to do it sideways.
Victoria@Between the fingers.
Emily@Is this okay?
Samantha@Grace, it feels so good.
Samantha@It's so erotic.
Victoria@This scene is so embarrassing.
Megan@Almost there.
Samantha@What are you doing?
Emily@It's really difficult.
Samantha@It feels so good.
Samantha@So comfortable.
Megan@I'm going to count down.
Samantha@The friction feels great.
Samantha@It feels so good. 10
Megan@9
Megan@8
Megan@7
Megan@6
Megan@5
@4
@3
@2
Megan@1
Megan@It didn't work.
Samantha@How could it fail?
Samantha@How did this happen?
Samantha@What should we do since Grace didn't succeed?
Victoria@Punishment.
Megan@It's punishment time!
Victoria@Hey.
Victoria@Isn't there supposed to be a punishment for losing?
Samantha@Yeah, there should be a punishment.
Samantha@Hmm, well...
Samantha@Let's leave that couple alone.
Alex@The punishment is over.
Samantha@That hardly counts as a punishment.
Samantha@That wasn't a punishment at all.
Samantha@What kind of punishment was that? It doesn't count.
Samantha@Me?
Samantha@Is there such a thing as punishment for me?
Samantha@I don't think so.
Victoria@Don't you love using dating apps?
Victoria@Why don't we swipe for you?
Victoria@And set up a hookup with someone.
Alex@I think that's a good idea.
Samantha@Bring it on. Sure, go ahead.
Victoria@You'll see in a moment.
Grace@I want to see too.
Samantha@What is it?
Grace@Is he handsome?
Victoria@Hey, this one uses dating apps a lot.
Samantha@No, I don't want this long-haired guy.
Victoria@Come on, you have to accept the bet's result.
Victoria@Go away.
Samantha@I just don't like long-haired guys.
Samantha@And you still made a date with him?
Victoria@I did.
Victoria@You're quite popular, huh?
Victoria@Long-haired guys can be okay too.
Samantha@I heard you still have an on-and-off ex-boyfriend?
Samantha@Want me to help you invite him over?
Victoria@You're such a gossip.
Victoria@Are you trying to break me and my boyfriend up?
Samantha@Let me tell you something.
Samantha@In this apartment,
Samantha@there are no secrets.
Samantha@And I'm just telling you to invite him over,
Samantha@not to do anything with him.
Victoria@Alright, you're really annoying.
Victoria@Wait a minute.
Victoria@Doesn't Emily have a crush on someone?
Samantha@Who?
Emily@No, I don't!
Emily@That's not true at all.
@She does.
Victoria@Come here.
Samantha@I'll help you.
Samantha@I'm telling you, I'm the best at this kind of thing.
Samantha@I'm really good at this.
Samantha@Come on, let me help you.
Grace@Grab her! Hold her!
Emily@No, stop it!
Grace@We're trying to help you!
Samantha@I'll help you.
Samantha@Can you come see me tonight?
Emily@No, don't!
Samantha@I have something to tell you.
Emily@Give it back!
Samantha@Hey, look!
Samantha@Look, he read it instantly! He read it right away!
Samantha@It worked!
Samantha@Success, success!
Samantha@Wait, we still have one more colleague.
Samantha@She's always been focused on work.
Samantha@Never had time to go out.
Emily@That's you!
Samantha@Come on, come on!
Samantha@I'll give you something good.
Grace@What's this?
Samantha@This is something I bought at an adult store.
Samantha@It's an aphrodisiac.
Megan@What's an aphrodisiac?
Samantha@It's like a love potion.
Samantha@Come on, come on.
Samantha@Let me add a couple of drops for you.
Emily@She's going to put it all in for you.
Samantha@Then I'll set you up with a hot guy later.
Samantha@And then you can try it out.
Samantha@Let me tell you.
Samantha@It makes me squirt.
Samantha@It'll definitely make you feel really good.
Samantha@Let me message him real quick.
Emily@Look at Grace's face.
Samantha@He says it's okay.
Emily@There really is someone.
Emily@Cheers!
Megan@Bottoms up!
Samantha@You're so brave!
Victoria@She's going all out.
Samantha@Your first time in years.
Victoria@Are you a virgin?
Grace@I've had experience before.
Emily@When was that?
@You're lying to us, right? -You look so innocent.
Megan@You were just jealous earlier.
Alex@I wasn't jealous.
Alex@Which eye of yours saw me being jealous?
Grace@I'll clean up a bit first.
Samantha@Are you guys going to sleep?
Emily@I want to tidy up a bit.
Grace@I still need to change my clothes.
Alex@Don't drink too much, okay?
Alex@You've had too much.
Alex@You're very drunk.
Alex@Look.
Alex@Your face is all red and you're still drinking.
Megan@It's so hot.
Alex@It's all the alcohol. What are you doing?
Megan@It's really hot!
Alex@You're sweating all over.
@What, do you want to lick it too? -Who wants to lick?
Megan@It's sticking up.
Alex@Pervert.
Alex@You're over there.
Megan@My head hurts so much.
Alex@I'll take you back to your room to sleep.
Megan@I want to go back to my room.
Alex@Hey, be careful, be careful!
Alex@What are you doing? Be careful, be careful!